Thomas Miccali

FINANCIAL SERVICES

1234 5th Ave • New York, NY 10010

(212) 123-4567

₹ ThomasMiccali@aol.com

Diligent and assertive *Marine Corp Veteran* **and Hofstra Graduate** with a *Bachelor's Degree in Finance* and completed coursework in: finance, economics and business and a sincere interest in the financial markets.

Strong leader and mentor who others refer to for: guidance, strength and encouragement in overwhelming, uncertain situations. Articulate communicator and concise presenter.

Demonstrated expertise includes: performing in collaborative team environments, leadership and astute crisis dilemma solving skills with adaptability to rapid changes in fast paced, high pressured surroundings.

VALUE ADDED

Leadership/Mentoring = Problem Diagnosis/Resolution = Quality Control = Variance Analysis = Client Services
Relationship Development/Management = Sales = Special Event Coordination = Subordinate Evaluations
Bloomberg = Microsoft Office = Word = *Excel = PowerPoint = Outlook

EDUCATION

New York University • Stern School of Business – *New York, NY* **Bachelor of Business Administration • Finance •** 2011

*Dean's List • 2010/2011

C. W. Post – *Brookville, NY*Associates Degree ■ Criminal Justice ■ 2009

MILITARY

United States Marine Corp Reserve ■ 1st Battalion ■ 23rd Marine Regiment ■ Corporal ■ 06/2001-08/2007

*Recipient of three promotions: Private → Private 1st Class → Lance Corporal → Corporal

DUTIES - FUNCTIONS & RESPONSIBILITIES

- Classified Information Correspondent
- Combat Action Veteran
- Cross Trained with Diverse Units
- Equipment Troubleshooter
- Evaluated Subordinates

- Military Occupation Field Radio Operator
- Safeguarded Sensitive/Top Secret Equipment
- Secret Level Security Clearance
- Squad Leader
- Supervised Eight Junior Marines

*Meritorious Promotion to Corporal

*Certificate of Commendation • Superior Performance of Duty as Field Communication Operator *Meritorious Mast Award • Field Communication Operator as Tactical Air Control Party Member

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Major Financial Institution – *New York, NY* **Intern to Financial Planner**

02/2011 - 06/2011

- Unpaid internship working with Senior Financial Planner with \$110 million assets under management.
- Evaluated/analyzed information, trends/performance utilizing Excel, and PowerPoint for presentations.
- Attended client and internal meetings, scheduled consultations and reviewed financial and economic news as it related to the markets and its impact on investments.
- Interacted and communicated with mutual fund portfolio managers for new investment opportunities.

Mangia Al Fresco – New York, NY Server

09/2007 - 12/2010

• Consistently ranked as a top server incorporating excellent customer service and communication skills.







America's #1 Online Resume Builder

With Cover Letters

- Easy-to-use, guides you through step-by-step
- Resume templates, writing samples and tips
- One-click designs for the professional look you want
- Start from scratch or upload your resume



Already have an account?











Phone and Chat Hours: 7 Days a Week 6am to midnight EST



Write a resume - in minutes

Your resume is often your first and only chance to make a great impression on an employer. Managers will scan your resume for just 10 seconds to see if you're right for the job.

That's why your resume needs to be attractive and stand out. It needs to be well-written and highlight your skills to your best advantage.

The problem is most people don't know how to write a great resume and don't have the design skills to make it look professional.

- Our Resume Builder is designed to make resume-writing fast and easy.
- We match you with the right template and, in just one click, you can choose a professional design that will help you win the job.
- Our unique Text Tuner™ allows you to choose from hundreds of expert-written examples - no more writer's block!

Get the "most impressive resume builder on the market today". There's no risk; no obligation. We're so confident that you'll love our resume builder that you can try it for FREE.

According to our partners..."the most impressive resume builder on the market today."

onTargetiobs

YAHOO! hotjobs EmploymentGuide.com

Ret-Temps Joined

Customer Reviews

Job.com

"I was completely unaware of what companies are looking for in a resume. This product helped me word and format my professional resume and the examples were extremely useful. Overall, this is a great product. I would highly recommend these services." - A. Danihels

"This resume tool is so much better than templates - just upload or enter your resume content and you get your choice of designs. It's magical! Anyone can benefit from this tool: from students to executives!" - Belinda Yanda

View more reviews >



